(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T02:06:23.952703",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Thank you all so much for coming to...
Takanashi Kiara and
Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, Drawn to Dawn!
Key!
Kiwawa!
I am Takanashi Kiara, and...
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
It's you know, my Ina'nis!
That's right, it's finally time
for our concert! Is everyone hyped?
Before we kick things off, we have some
important safety rules and guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of any recording
equipment are strictly prohibited during the show.
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
But what? But what if I'm smoking hot?
Minus Kiara! Haha!
If you start feeling unwell at any point,
please don't push yourself, just reach out for help and hydrate.
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This includes mosh-ing... no mosh-ing!
I mean it! Mosh-ing, diving,
sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects towards the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, blocking aisles, or rushing toward the front is also not allowed.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting or erratic lightstick movements,
or extreme motions that might interfere with others. Be considerate.
If you don't follow staff instructions, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Please keep in mind that the venue and staff cannot be held responsible for accidents
or equipment damage caused by failing to follow instructions.
Additionally, costs for damages from ignoring rules will be your responsibility,
so be careful, guys, okay?
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today, and you might appear in footage.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
Y'all are looking cute.
And finally... big news! Today's concert will be in two parts!
There's a part for Kiara and a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
All right, that is it for the rules! The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
さあ 散らばってしまった話を
Now, the stories that scattered away...
空に手を伸ばし始める
I begin to reach my hands toward the sky.
下を通り過ぎる曲がった線に 縛られた足をくすぐるの
Tickling the feet bound by twisted lines passing below.
落ちて汚れた意識を 名前と呪術にかけて
Casting a sigh, my fallen, tainted consciousness into names and sorcery.
空っぽだけだった身体の 夢見ていたまぶたが開く
The eyelids that dreamed of an empty body open up.
心の奥からうごめく記憶が 混じった呪いと祝福が目の前を
Memories stirring deep within, a mix of curse and blessing before my eyes...
（知ってるの？）
(Do you know?)
始まりと終わりに向かって 果てに戻ってくるのはパパの呼び声だけ
Heading toward beginning and end, what returns to the edge is only Papa's call.
父なる神よ、そこに居たら教えて欲しいの
Oh Father God, if you are there, I want you to tell me—
私が歩くこの道は どんな色だろう
What color is the path that I walk upon?
さあ この調べの旋律を
Now, the melody of this tune—
空に手を伸ばし始める
I begin to reach my hands toward the sky.
散らばった多くの血の道が 愛を渇望して泣き叫んでいる
The many paths of blood scattered about cry out, yearning for love.
始まりと終わりに向かって 果てに帰ってくるのは救われなかった君の声
Heading toward beginning and end, what returns to the edge is your unsaved voice.
愛しい妹よ そこに居たら教えて
Oh dear sister, if you are there, tell me—
君の手をいつかまた握れるのかな
Will I ever be able to hold your hand once again?
瞬く星のゆりかご
The cradle of twinkling stars,
欠けた台詞を繋ぎ合わせた memory
memory of piecing together broken lines.
聖なる従者が伝える神話の理
The myth's logic passed down by the holy follower,
祈りに耳を澄ませ
listen closely to the prayer.
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me 声なき声に
tell me, to the voiceless voice.
荒ぶる心拍は弱さを焦がす
The raging heartbeat burns away weakness.
炎降り注ぐ空に身を窶して
Hiding my body in the sky where flames pour down,
乱れ咲く赤は紅化粧
the scattering red is crimson makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive the countless trials that pile up.
I will live to keep on fighting till the dawn
たとえば先の見えない零の境界
Even if I wander into the zero boundary
迷い込んだとしても
where the end cannot be seen,
何度も繰り返される孤高の終焉
the lonely end that is repeated many times,
そこに残った answer
the answer left there.
Don't break, I will never give up
Don't break 羽が朽ちても
don't break, even if the wings rot.
消せない強さは時の導
The unquenchable strength is the guide of time.
灰花舞い上がる大地身をくぐらせ
The ash flowers dance in the sky, passing through the earth,
燃える朱の中目を目覚めさせる
I awaken within the burning vermilion.
刃交わる切先 交わした誓いは
The crossing blades, the vow we exchanged...
Lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark?
Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me 声なき声に
tell me, to the voiceless voice.
漲る決意は闇を晴らす
The rising determination clears the darkness.
炎降り注ぐ空に身を窶して
Hiding my body in the sky where flames pour down,
乱れ咲く赤は紅化粧
the scattering red is crimson makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive the countless trials that pile up.
Blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
And in the next life too, I promise, I will find you
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark?
Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me 声なき声に
tell me, to the voiceless voice.
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me 声なき声に
tell me, to the voiceless voice.
満つる願いは 影を晴らす
The swelling wish clears the shadows.
炎降り注ぐ空に身を窶して
Hiding my body in the sky where flames pour down,
乱れ咲く赤は紅化粧
the scattering red is crimson makeup.
数多重なる試練も生き抜いてみせる
I will survive the countless trials that pile up.
炎降り注ぐ空に身を窶して
Hiding my body in the sky where flames pour down,
乱れ咲く赤は紅化粧
the scattering red is crimson makeup.
Blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
And in the next life too, I promise, I will find you
Lying down on the floor late night
and you don't know, don't know
Don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right
if yes or no, don't know
Don't know what to do
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Just take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it
If you want it, let's get to it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks like the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up
And never be afraid
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
Don't stop
Just go your own way
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
Going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
That's how we like it, you heard what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So take a step and move it, move it
'Less you try, you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up
And never be afraid
Let go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive
From the ashes you rise
'Cause sparks light the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up
And never be afraid
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
Don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up
And never be afraid
Gotta make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table
To the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait
Start a fire today
Don't stop
Just go your own way
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up
And never be afraid
Hello, welcome everybody to...
Takanashi Kiara and you know what, this is first ever concert...
drawn to you!
I can hear you guys so clearly and I can see you guys so clearly!
Oh my god! We're in Los Angeles!
Yay!
So we started off with the iconic and classic songs of mine, Hinotori and Sparks.
Don't we love those songs? Wasn't it hype?
Yeah, you guys know like Hinotori was my first ever original song to put out...
history, my musical journey, and it's a song that means a lot to me,
and it's just so hype. It was also the first ever time that I appeared in 3D, I think,
long time ago at fest in Japan, right, remember?
Good times. Yeah!
Thank you so much for cheering so loudly, you did so well!
Yeah!
I have been training so hard the past months in the gym, trying to get stamina for this day,
because I think I learned about, learned and relearned about 20 choreographies.
Yeah!
Damn, that was a lot of work. But finally the day has come to show it to all of you.
I want to say hi, by the way, to all the live viewers worldwide!
There's so many cinemas showing this concert right now!
Hello world!
Can you hear me? I wonder if I can hear them.
Can I hear them over the continents?
Well, that's you guys!
Well, I think I can hear them. Yeah!
Also, there is Senchou Marine's watching on YouTube right now, like Ollie and all the EN members.
Hi, thank you!
So excited!
I have to give a little bit of an announcement from my side, actually,
because it's very important. This has to be in the free part, because everybody needs to hear this.
My new album, Hoshigirai,
you got it, right?
Thank you!
But in case you didn't, a second round of album sales has begun!
So if you missed it previously or you want a new copy, starting from Saturday, March 28th at 11:00 PM,
we'll find out, probably tasty, you will be able to order Hoshigirai again.
So please everybody, order Hoshigirai!
So far the songs that I performed up until now were not even from Hoshigirai,
but don't worry, I'm squeezing everything in that I can.
Okay guys, you probably aware of this, but the free part usually ends after an MC.
But free part, you only had two songs?
Nah, nah, nah, nah. Don't worry, I told staff,
we can't be having that. I want the free part to have a little bit more, yeah.
So it will continue a little bit more and then it will cut before our MC. So just so you know.
And then once it cuts, please streaming tickets are available still in the description and in the pinned comments.
Yes, so make sure to get your ticket because what you haven't even seen yet is my colleague,
Ninomae Ina'nis, right?
The concert is split in half, so today you only have me in the free part, but later if you want to see more of Walla and Ina, go get streaming tickets!
So with that, it is time to move on to many other songs. All right.
Are you ready?
All right, here is the next song, enjoy!
passing by familiar roads
i couldn't find the reason why
who i am you couldn't know
stuck in the ruins, my disillusion
in between a dual reality
my own desire keeps me to you, ooh
moving faster than the light can
i'm in the absence, alone looking back
did i lose my way, i can't see the day
when i can reach you again then can i let go?
i can hear your voice leading me through the void
fade away to the grey
I'm tired of the same song
Everyday like it's on repeat
I need a risque breakdown
Oh honey, the night is calling
Don't need a steady simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away like it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music? Baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light, come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
(Feel it rush through me)
Let this new sound take over me (Intoxicating, DJ keep playing)
Woah
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now, honey, follow me
I need a thrilling red-hot melody
Something to keep me up all night
Don't look away, now it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music? Baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light, come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
(Feel it rush through me)
この 心 の 音 を 合わせ て
Yeah, follow my heart beat
Bada da da da da da da di da
聞か せ て あげる
心 の bada ba badi
合わせ て follow my heart beat
Crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
You got me shining glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild
Don't care who's watching us
So baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light, come alive
Moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat get me dancing
(Feel it rush through me)
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
(Feel it rush through me)
Baby, can we dance until the daylight
Crazy about this sound I'm making with you
Woah
I'm tired of the same song
Everyday like it's on repeat
I need a risque breakdown
Oh honey, the night is calling
Don't need a steady simple melody
Can you make it original?
Take me away like it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music? Baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light, come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
(Feel it rush through me)
Let this new sound take over me (Intoxicating, DJ keep playing)
Woah
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now, honey, follow me
I need a thrilling red-hot melody
Something to keep me up all night
Don't look away, now it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music? Baby
Meet me underneath the strobe light, come alive
Move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat get me dancing
(Feel it rush through me)
Baby, can we dance until the daylight
Crazy about this sound I'm making with you
Woah